let onset_trials = [
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'b_group', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'onset-coda', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '1', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '2', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_00_00', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_08_01', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '8', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_08_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_14_02', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_14_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_19_03', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_19_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_23_04', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_23_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_25_05', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_25_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_26_06', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_26_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_27_07', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_27_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_28_08', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_28_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_29_09', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '29', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_29_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAA_PAA_3_30_10', vowel: 'AA', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '25', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAA_PAA_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_00_00', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_05_01', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_10_02', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '10', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_10_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_14_03', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_14_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_17_04', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '17', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_17_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_19_05', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '19', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_19_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_20_06', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_20_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_22_07', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '22', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_22_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_24_08', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_24_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_27_09', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '27', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_27_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BAH_PAH_3_30_10', vowel: 'AH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '19', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BAH_PAH_3_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_00_00', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_06_01', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '6', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_06_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_11_02', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '11', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_11_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_16_03', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_16_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_20_04', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '20', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_20_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_23_05', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '23', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_23_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_24_06', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '24', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_24_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_25_07', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_25_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_26_08', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '26', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_26_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_28_09', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '28', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_28_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BIH_PIH_5_30_10', vowel: 'IH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '23', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BIH_PIH_5_30_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_00_00', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '0', tone_step: '0', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_00_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_05_01', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '5', tone_step: '1', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_05_01.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_09_02', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '9', tone_step: '2', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_09_02.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_12_03', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '12', tone_step: '3', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_12_03.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_14_04', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '14', tone_step: '4', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_14_04.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_15_05', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '15', tone_step: '5', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_15_05.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_16_06', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '16', tone_step: '6', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_16_06.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_18_07', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '18', tone_step: '7', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_18_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_21_08', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '21', tone_step: '8', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_21_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_25_09', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '25', tone_step: '9', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_25_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>P</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>B</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'coda-onset', test_part: 'test_onset', correct_response: 'NA', group: 'control', type: 'onset_syllable', audio: 'BUH_PUH_3_30_10', vowel: 'UH', visual_target: 'NA', repetition: '3', normed_midpoint: '15', voiced_sel: 'B', voiceless_sel: 'P', match_sel: 'NA', mismatch_sel: 'NA', step: '30', tone_step: '10', path: 'audio/onset_syllables/BUH_PUH_3_30_10.wav' }}]